Arpit Gaurav Alne 
Senior RPA Developer 
 arpitalne619@gmail.com github.com/arpit-alne 
  +91 9284825897  linkedin.com/in/arpit-alne 
PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY                                                                                                                                                                            
Certified Blue Prism professional and results-driven RPA Developer with 5 yearsÆ experience in Blue Prism RPA technology, 
delivering robust, end-to-end automations from design to go-live. Proven ability to cut manual processing time by up to 80%, 
automate 1,000+ hours annually, and improve process accuracy by 25%, with operational cost savings. Skilled in C#, SQL, 
HTML, JavaScript, and JIRA, with a track record of streamlining complex business processes at scale. 
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE                                                                                                                                                                     
1. Company Name : Perficient, Inc. 
ò Designation : Automation û Senior RPA Developer 
ò Duration  : July 2021 û March 2026  
ò Responsibilities :  
o Delivered 20+ automation projects built primarily in Blue Prism, leveraging key components such as Objects, 
Processes, Work Queues, Schedules, and Credentials, resulting in a 50û60% reduction in manual effort.  
o Collaborated with business analysts and SMEs to identify and automate complex workflows, ensuring scalable 
and business-aligned automation solutions. 
o Conducted unit testing, debugging, and production support, maintaining process stability and continuously 
improving automation reliability. 
o Worked across multiple automation platforms including UiPath, Appian, Microsoft Power Automate and 
ServiceNow ITMS tool applying best practices to design scalable, high-performing RPA solutions. 
2. Company Name : CGI 
ò Designation : Senior Software Engineer 
ò Duration  : March 2026 û Present 
ò Responsibilities :  
o Provided L2/L3 production support for Blue Prism automations and ensured smooth business operations  
o Monitored bots and queues through Control Room, handled failed sessions, and ensured SLA compliance 
 
TECHNICAL SKILLS                                                                                                                                                                                              
 
PROJECTS WORKED ON                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         
1. Project Title                               : Duplicates Claim Management and Enhancement 
Client : Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts (BCBSMA) 
Application used  : RPA û Blueprism, Mainframe Application, Excel, Web Application, Salesforce API 
 Briefing                 : The Duplicate Claim Check process reviews claim history across multiple applications to 
identify and manage duplicate claims by checking if a service has already been paid.  Developed end-to-end automation 
solutions, reducing manual processing time by 40%. Improved accuracy of duplicate claim detection by 25%, resulting in 
ò RPA Tool:  
o Blue Prism v7.x (Advance) 
o UiPath, Power Automate Desktop (Basic) 
ò RPA components - Process Studio, Object Studio, Work 
Queue, Control Room, Schedular, Package, System Manager, 
UiPath Studio, UiPath REFramework, Orchestrator, Version 
Control, Login Agent, Credential Manager, Environment 
Variable, Web API Services. 
ò Automation Type : Web, Desktop, Mainframe, Excel , PDF, 
Email, Database Automation, Surface Automation, SAP, API, 
OCR. 
ò Programming Languages:  HTML, CSS, 
JavaScript, Python, Java, C#, VB, SQL. 
ò REST / SOAP API 
ò JIRA / ServiceNow Ticketing Tool 
ò Generative AI 
ò N8N 
ò Documentation: PDD, SDD, Test Case, Process 
Flow and Reporting. 

significant cost savings. 
2. Project Title : RTMS Mainframe Application Screen Scrap  
Client : Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts (BCBSMA) 
Application used   : RPA û Blueprism, Mainframe Application, MS Word, PDF, Excel  
Briefing : This process is to capture the information  of various plans from RTMS Application and 
Generate the PDF file of various screen of RTMS, significantly reduced the manual effort involved in validating plans 
3. Project Title : Update RTMS and Member Rights Comments Process  
Client : Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts (BCBSMA) 
Application used   : RPA û Blueprism, Mainframe Application, Excel  
 Briefing : The Update RTMS and Member Rights Comments process involves retrieving case 
comments from Appian via API, updating them in the RTMS Mainframe and SQL Database, and developing a reporting 
bot to send daily QC reports. 
4. Project Title : QC Process for Update Comments Process  
Client : Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts (BCBSMA) 
Application used   : RPA û Blueprism, Mainframe Application, Excel, Web Application 
 Briefing : The process involves validating member information and comments in a third -party 
application for QC. If discrepancies are found, a Business Exception is sent. After correction, the QC bot reprocesses the 
case. Additionally, a reporting bot sends daily QC reports, that helps business team efficiency. 
5. Project Title : Provider Suppression and Un-Suppression  
Client : Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts (BCBSMA) 
Application used   : RPA û Blueprism, Excel, Sympler Web Application, Salesforce API 
 Briefing :The Provider Suppression and Un-Suppression process automates checking/unchecking 
the 'Directory Exclusion' checkbox in the Cactus Application based on Excel inputs. This bot reduces errors and cuts down 
manual efforts from 10 min to 2 min and generates a report for review. 
6. Project Title : Invoice Processing Workflow 
Application used   : RPA û Power Automate Desktop, Outlook, PDF 
Briefing : Invoice Processing Automation simplifies the entire workflow ù from receiving invoices 
via email to recording them in the ERP system. The Bot automatically extracts key details from PDFs, validates the data, 
and inputs it seamlessly using Power Automate Desktop.  It then generates an Excel report and sends a summary email, 
significantly reducing manual effort, minimizing errors, and improving overall efficiency. 
ACADEMIC DETAILS                                                                                                                                                                                 
 
CERTIFICATION                                                                                                                                                                                                     
ò Blue Prism Certified Associate Developer û Link 
ò Blue Prism Certified Developer û Link 
ò Blue Prism Professional Certification (LinkedIn) - Link 
ò UiPath Automation Training Certificate of Completion 12 
hours - Link 
ò Blue Prism Professional Developer Certificate of 
Completion 98 hours - Link 
ò Power Automate Certificate (Udemy) - Link 
ò ServiceNow Certified System Administrator - Link 
ò Appreciation and Shoutout - Link 
 
 
Year Degree University/Board School/College CGPA 
2017-21 BE (IT) Rashtrasant Tukdoji Maharaj 
Nagpur University 
S.B Jain Institute of Technology 
Management & Research 8.20 
2016-17 H.S.C CBSE Reliance Foundation school 6.20 
2014-15 S.S.C CBSE Reliance Foundation school 6.60 


